Viewers all over the world - locate me Lord, in Your mercy; locate me Lord, in Your favour!
Don't leave me out when You are delivering others!
Prayer Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Begin to throw them back - that affliction in your blood, bones, kidney, liver, in the name of Jesus!
Say after me: Locate me Lord! Locate me Lord, in Your mercy! Locate me Lord in Your favour!
Lord Jesus, every trouble that troubles my body, that troubles my life,
every affliction that troubles my life - leave in the name of Jesus!
Wherever it is located, that affliction, I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
I say wherever it is located that affliction, I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Every affliction troubling your life,
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever it is located that affliction, I command you out, in the name of Jesus!
I command you out, in the name of JESUS!
Let every trouble receive solution!
In your business, receive solution!
In your career, receive solution!
In your family, receive solution!
In your marriage, receive solution!
In your relationship receive solution!
Solution, in the name of Jesus!
Prayer Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
My business - here is solution!
My career - here is solution!
My marriage - here is solution!
Prayer Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
My family - here is solution!
My health - here is solution!
In the name of Jesus!
Rejoice!
Viewers, you know prayer has a language.
This is prayer for you.
These prayers are anointed.
With all your heart, speak to your heart.
Locate me in Your mercy, oh Lord. Locate me in your favor, oh Lord.
Bless you!
Prayer Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Juliet Bwalya 28/09/18
RV ROBERT BEGIER 29/09/2018